{
    "id": "97719dcf876b441295daa5733cb55cb8",
    "title": "Articles Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Yesterday I heard ……………………. interesting story which is …………………… best I have ever heard.",
            "description": "A/An can mean one use the before superlatives. ",
            "answers": [
                "the, the",
                "an, a",
                "an, the"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I saw ………………………….. pretty woman in the store.",
            "description": "When it is not clear which person or thing we are talking about, we use a. ",
            "answers": [
                "the",
                "a"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Ceylon is ………………………… island in ……………………….. Indian Ocean.",
            "description": "Use a with the meaning of one.",
            "answers": [
                "an, an",
                "an, the",
                "the, the"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He has ……………………….. keen eye for detail.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He was ……………………….. only child of ……………………… rich merchant.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "an, the",
                "the, the",
                "the, a"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "We expect ………………………….. official inquiry into the incident.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………. person who died yesterday was …………………………. heart patient.",
            "description": "Use the to talk about a particular person use a when you are not talking about anyone in particular. ",
            "answers": [
                "A, a",
                "The, a",
                "The, the"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Son, ‘I want ……………………… pencil.’ Mother, ‘Where is ………………………… pencil I gave you yesterday?’",
            "description": "Use a when you are talking about a person or thing for the first time use the in subsequent references to that person or thing. ",
            "answers": [
                "a, the",
                "the, the",
                "a, a"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I saw …………………………….. old man. He was carrying ………………………… umbrella.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a, an",
                "an, an",
                "a, a"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I saw ………………………………… rhino in …………………….. zoo.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "the, a",
                "a, the",
                "a, an"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "May is …………………………. hottest month of ………………………. year.",
            "description": "Use the with superlatives. ",
            "answers": [
                "the, the",
                "the, a",
                "a, the"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "There is …………………………… school for ……………………………… blind in this city.",
            "description": "The blind means all blind people a school means one school. ",
            "answers": [
                "a, the",
                "the, the",
                "a, a"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}